Behnam Moein

24 year old computer science graduate from The University of Salford, e web developer with almost a year of experience in industry. Worked remotely throughout Covid in the council but am looking for more complex hands-on work in the office now that quarantine has ended. Open to working remotely 2-3 days a week. See portfolio at **Behnammoein.com**

13 Newbold Street
Bury, Greater Manchester,
BL8 2RR
07526259415
Behnam789@hotmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tameside Council, Ashton—Web Developer

January 2020- PRESENT

Managing databases in SQL that take the data from web forms that I also designed. We use classic asp in the .NET framework for the older applications and C# and MVC in newer applications.

Pizza Express, Bury—Pot Wash

September 2019 - October 2019

Opening the store, in the morning and closing at night. Washing the pots for the kitchen during opening hours.

Bierkeller, Manchester - Barback / Bartender

January 2019 - September 2019

Part time job during university, started as a barback and finished as a bartender

EDUCATION

Salford University, Salford—Bachelor's Degree - Computer Science

September 2016- July 2019

Projects with the following oo technologies: Java, C#, Swift - Web frameworks - HTML, CSS and Javascript

Holy Cross College = Bury — A Levels

2012 - 2014

A Levels in Physics, Mathematics, Biology and General Studies

PERSONAL INFORMATION

github.com/citywok11 linkedin.com/in/behnam-mo ein-b452a6192/

AWARDS

Querying Microsoft SQL Server - QA Consulting - This was a week-long course paid for by the council

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES / FRAMEWORKS

In Tameside Council I worked with the .NET tech stack which encompassed:

- Classic ASP (VB Script)
- MSSQL
- C#

Alongside this in the council I also extended my knowledge of the following general web development technologies:

- HTML5
- CSS (Bootstrap 3)
- Javascript/JQuery